indiatradepage.com 2016-03-12

# PRIVACY POLICY Indiatradepage.com - Indian Exporters, Importers, service providers, Manufacturers directory and Yellow Pages India, India Yellow Pages.

Indiatradepage.com is completely committed to protect its users' privacy. We request you to read this privacy policy before or as soon as you start using Indiatradepage.com. As soon as you use this website, you agree to our Privacy Policy defined below. The 'privacy policy' will help you understand how your personal and business information will be managed at Indiatradepage.com, as you use our service for you business benefits. 

**Information Collected**  
Indiatradepage.com will collect your personal and business information when you register yourself with Indiatradepage.com to access its services or at any other time when Indiatradepage.com request you to provide it the same for any specific purpose. The registration form will ask for your name, address, phone/fax number, email address and other personal information as well as information about your business. 

As a registered user of Indiatradepage.com you give full authority to Indiatradepage.com to publish the business and personal details throughout its marketplaces, including but not limited to, business directory, trade leads, catalogs, etc.

We will also collect your payment information if you establish a credit account with our providers or us at the time of your buying a product or service from Indiatradepage.com or a vendor available through Indiatradepage.com. We may possibly gather information, including but not limited to, billing information, credit card numbers and expiration dates and tracking information from cheques or money orders.

Apart from all these, we collect comprehensive information regarding our website and Users, such as IP addresses, browser software, operating system, pages viewed, number of sessions, unique visitors and so forth.

In addition to it, once your personal and business information is displayed on our network, you may start receiving business inquiries from various buyers and sellers that may or may not be of your interest. Indiatradepage.com does not have any control over such business inquiries send by its users to the listed members.

**Use of Information**  
The information collected is used to improve our marketing and promotional efforts to improve our content and product offerings and to customize our website's content, layout and service exclusively to get hold of maximum business opportunities for the users. We may perhaps make use of your gathered information to service your Account with us, together with, however not restricted to inspecting troubles, resolve disagreements and imposing agreements with us. We do not engage ourselves in selling, renting, trading or swapping any personally identifying information of our users. Though, we may well share definite collective information standing on study of gathered Information with our partners, customers, advertisers or potential users. The collected information might be taken in use from our side to carry out marketing promotion, advertising messages on behalf of third parties; though, in these state of affairs, you will observe a complete security of your information that will not be revealed to such third parties unless you act in response to the marketing, promotion or advertising message.

**Disclosure of Information**  
Indiatradepage.com will not disclose or share its users personal or any other identifiable information except in the reason where it believes that such revelation is obligatory to recognize, get in touch with or take lawful action against someone who may be breaching the laws or intimidating to breach, or who may perhaps otherwise be creating damage to or intrusion with, the title, rights, interests or property of Indiatradepage.com, its users, customers, partners, other web site users or anyone else who possibly will be injured by such activities.

Moreover, Indiatradepage.com reserves the rights to reveal users information where it convincingly believes that such revelation are mandatory by rule, directive or governmental order of any court, legislative or regulatory authority.

If we have reason to believe that a user is in violation of the Terms of User Agreement or any other agreement with us, afterward we retain the right to disclose or make public such user's Information in order to follow our claim or to prevent further damage to Indiatradepage.com or others.

**Correction of Information  **  
Anytime, you have the right to access, inspect and revise your personal, business and payment information (if any) all the way through your Account with Indiatradepage.com. 

**Security Measures**  
We take up commercially logical protection ways to put off unlawful access, preserve data precision and guarantee proper use of information. 

Being a Registered User, you will observe the editing and viewing of the Registration Information, Publishing Information and Payment Information through your Account that is protected by Password. We suggest you not to reveal your Password to anyone, and our staff will in no way solicit you for your Password through any unwanted phone call or in an unwelcome e-mail. You must avoid saving your login information (e.g., User ID and Password) on the computer when you are sharing a computer with others. Keep in mind forever to sign out of your Account and close your browser window as soon as you have ended your session. 

You should also recognize that no data communication over the Internet or any wireless network can be assured to be absolutely protected. Though we attempt our level best to protect your information, even after knowing that no website or company, together with ourselves, can extremely guarantee or promise the safety of any information you send out to us and, you do so at your own risk. 

**Updation of Information** A user may edit his/her account information and profile by logging onto our website and/or by sending a request to admin@indiatradepage.com. The requested changes may take upto 30 days to appear online because of verification process and server cache policies. 

A user account can be deleted or deactivated, but doing so will result in the user not being able to access any members-only area of the network. Residual information will remain within our archive records. 

**Changes to Privacy Policy**  
The Privacy Policy may change from time to time. The amended Privacy Policy will be posted here for your purpose. The amended policy will be effective from the day it is posted on the website.

**Your feedback  **  
Indiatradepage.com welcomes your constant input on the topic of Privacy Policy or services presented to you. You could mail us your remarks and reactions at [contact@Indiatradepage.com](mailto:contact@Indiatradepage.com)
